<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ignacio Villanueva - Frontend developer focused on performance, responsive design, web typography and accessibility.</title>
    <description>Focused on performance, responsive design, web typography and accessibility</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 20:56:18 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 20:56:18 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.4</generator>
    
      
        <item>
          <title>FrontFest 2019</title>
          <description>Como cada año, y esta es la tercera edición, hemos asistido al FrontFest, un evento para la comunidad. Esta vez no ha sido menos. En este post voy a hablaros sobre todo de lo que significa para mi y lo que he vivido como organizador. Casi todo ha sido bueno, pero aún podemos mejorar cosas.</description>
          <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2019/02/11/frontfest-2019/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019/02/11/frontfest-2019/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Resumen del 2017</title>
          <description>El año pasado vi que algunos desarrolladores publicaban lo que había sido su 2016 y me apunté el hacer un artículo al respecto, así que allá va. ¿Qué he hecho en 2017? Me ha cambiado la vida, profesionalmente sobre todo, he dado un salto de gigante. Espero estar a la altura.</description>
          <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2018/01/08/resumen-del-2017/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2018/01/08/resumen-del-2017/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Hombres, nuestra responsabilidad en el sector</title>
          <description>He sido machista, bueno, lo soy, pero creo que están en todos mejorar como personas e intentar hacerle lo más fácil posible la vida a quienes nos rodean, no por palabrearía, si no, ¿para qué estar todo el día a malas? Somos gran parte del problema, toca cambiarlo.</description>
          <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/09/25/hombres-nuestra-responsabilidad-en-el-sector-del-desarrollo/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/09/25/hombres-nuestra-responsabilidad-en-el-sector-del-desarrollo/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>TheAntiEvent 2017</title>
          <description>¿Sabe cuándo crees que has encontrado el tipo de evento que más te gusta? Después del IndieWebCamp Brighton 2016 (un open-space), puedo decir que es el tipo evento donde más cómodo me siento, supongo que es por su informalidad y deseo de compartir.</description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/09/12/the-anti-event/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/09/12/the-anti-event/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>IndieWebCamp Brighton 2016</title>
          <description>Since I'm in the Web industry I've already been to several events, although it is true that there are things I like more of some than others this time has been incredible, going to meet people whom I admire professionally, to another country has been spectacular.</description>
          <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/10/06/indie-web-camp-brighton-2016/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/10/06/indie-web-camp-brighton-2016/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>On being overwhelmed</title>
          <description>You know that feeling where you think everything's going faster than you'd like? It's happened to me, well, I really suppose it happens to many of us, there are so many new things that you won't be able to learn everything. I had the feeling that I'll never know enough.</description>
          <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/05/03/on-being-overwhelmed/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/05/03/on-being-overwhelmed/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Why I chose Jekyll to develop my website</title>
          <description>When you start in the sector you don't know what to use to create your projects... There are so many different tools that you go crazy! It happened to me, I didn't know if to use a WordPress, to do everything by hand without help... So I decided on Jekyll.</description>
          <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/04/24/why-i-chose-jekyll-to-develop-my-website/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/04/24/why-i-chose-jekyll-to-develop-my-website/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Uses</title>
          <description>In this post I will try to compile the things I use to work in my day to day, computer, peripherals such as mouse, desktop, chair and above all, software. I think that we focus a lot on things of little importance and other more necessary things we overlook.</description>
          <pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/04/17/uses/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/04/17/uses/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Passion for Web Development</title>
          <description>I always wanted to devote myself to the graphic arts industry, they made me happy, unfortunately for some time now, my old sector was not going well. The company he worked for went broke, so I decided to change. I have arrived to stay! Someday, I'll be a senior.</description>
          <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/03/04/passion-for-web-development/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/03/04/passion-for-web-development/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>My interest in web development</title>
          <description>Everyone has a clear interest in their job, some people are just a means to survive and pay bills, which, flatter, is completely normal, to other people, we happen to love our profession (let's not fall into the classicism with this, please). Do you like your job?</description>
          <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/02/28/my-interest-in-web-development/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/02/28/my-interest-in-web-development/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>My next step learning and New Year's Resolutions</title>
          <description>You start in this industry, knowing almost nothing. So, for this year I have made decisions on how to focus my future and what to learn. For that reason, I thought that the next clear step will be to start learning JavaScript well. Here are some ideas about it.</description>
          <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/02/18/my-next-step-learning-and-new-years-resolutions/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/02/18/my-next-step-learning-and-new-years-resolutions/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Interviewing Web People</title>
          <description>I've started in the industry not knowing a lot, so I've decided to ask people I admire if they would like to answer a small interview for my web, so I can know what you can do as junior developer to start learning, what things are more importand and so on. Here is the why.</description>
          <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2015/12/04/Interviewing-web-people/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2015/12/04/Interviewing-web-people/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
      
        <item>
          <title>Hello World</title>
          <description>Hi! First clarify that this is going to be the blog of my personal trip into Frontend Develpment, where I'll be sharing my thougts on many topics related to Web Industry, CSS and Sass, architecture, frontend performance, accessibility, typography and responsive web design.</description>
          <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
          <link>http://localhost:4000/2015/11/25/hello-world/</link>
          <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2015/11/25/hello-world/</guid>
        </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
